He really is strong.
Zentos Ordi isn't captain of the
second battalion for nothing.
His physical abilities are
simply better than mine.
That kick was hardly chivalrous.
It's what my master taught me.
Seriously?
That's a fine blade.
Thanks.
Say, let me ask again. Will you surrender?
I don't want you to die.
If you're so desperate to save me,
I wish you'd let me kill you.
You're asking a little much.
I can't let this drag on any longer.
I have to make a play to finish things.
Here he comes!
With my next attack, I'll kill you
and go after the princess.
I would ask your name first.
It's Kyle. Kyle Leonard.
I hope you'll remember it.
Indeed I shall...
Kyle Leonard!
Until now, I've wielded my sword
for my kingdom and the royal family.
That was my rightful role,
and I was proud to fulfill it.
Everything for the kingdom, huh?
Honestly, I didn't have a very
favorable impression of Zirgus's king.
Nevertheless, the nation
I swore my life to is gone.
Now I wield my sword for myself.
Is that hard for you?
No.
I feel as if I've been liberated.
Did you deliberately allow me
to deflect your blade?
No, that was for real.
You warded me off at my full strength.
But I did know you'd deflect the blow
and go for the kill.
Because that's the Zentos Ordi
I know and trust.
You're a strange man.
Forgive me...
I'm sorry.
There are things I want to protect,
no matter what it takes.
You were one of them, Zentos.
Farewell, my brother in arms.
What's going on? What could be happening?!
Zentos! You're late!
What are you—
Excuse us, Your Highness.
Search every nook and cranny!
Ma'am!
Wh-Who are you?!
On whose authority—
How do you do, brother?
Kilren, seize Prince Carenas
and interrogate him.
If need be, you may use force.
At once.
Unhand me!
Who do you think I am?!
I am the eldest son of King Remonas—
I owe you all my deepest gratitude.
No, thank you for trusting us.
Guess this settles your little family feud.
Yes, this will be the end of it.
Allow me to thank you formally
at the royal capital.
Castles are incredible!
To be honest, I feel ill at ease here.
Delicious! This is truly delicious!
Hey, missy. Let's get tea sometime.
More!
Sorry they all lack restraint.
You needn't be so tense.
Milena!
Father!
You're all right.
Yes. I apologize for worrying you.
Wait, if that's the princess's dad, then...
He's the king!
Milena, you're quite certain in your report?
Yes.
These are the people who rescued me.
That's all right. This isn't a public display.
I stand here to thank you
not as king, but as a father.
You're too kind.
It's a shame about Carenas,
but why was Zentos helping him?
It could be the meddling of another nation,
or perhaps demons were involved.
We should investigate discreetly.
I'm sure you were listening,
but you must tell no one of this.
Is that understood?
Of course.
We'd never tell anyone anything
that would harm the kingdom of Zirgus.
Yeah!
We can trust these people.
I see. If you say so, then I believe it.
You have my word you'll be rewarded
appropriately for your deeds.
The citizenry was immediately
informed of the incident.
Princess Milena and Prince Carenas
were attacked by a horde of monsters
while on their way to Sanes Village.
Over half of the second battalion fell
in the attack, including Captain Zentos.
Furthermore, Prince Carenas was badly wounded
and sent to Kourtim to recuperate.
That was the official story.
Only a handful knew the truth.
Kyle Leonard and companions,
you most nobly rescued
Princess Milena from grave danger.
For this great feat, I grant
you the Saint Randenaire Medal.
I humbly accept.
Marvelous!
He's a hero!
A hero is born!
"Hope of humanity."
"Master of sword and magic."
"The lecherous hero."
This was the moment a great hero
who would come to be known
by many names first made
his appearance in history.
This is where Kyle the hero's new saga begins.
Carenas and Zentos were both utterly useless.
When I someday relinquish the throne,
Milena will be crowned queen.
As extraordinary as she is,
she'll build a better Zirgus,
leaving me to be remembered
not as king... but as her father!
I will be second to her!
I have to hurry! I have to come up
with a new plan soon!
Good evening, King Remonas.
Wh-Who are you?
How did you get in?!
During the Great Invasion,
I made a suggestion to you.
I asked you to aid the dwarves
in the next kingdom over.
However, wanting to have the upper hand
in diplomatic relations,
you insisted you'd only help
once they were in danger
and withheld aid until then.
The dwarves were destroyed as a result.
It was a defeat with lasting impact,
spelling Zirgus's downfall.
Of course, I wasn't going to hold something
you hadn't done yet against you.
But now...
Forgive me, Your Majesty.
W-Wait.
Now that I think about it, it's simple.
The only one who could send
Zentos to kill the princess...
was you, Your Majesty.
What of it?
If he had succeeded, there'd be no problem!
If only he could've chosen
the nation he served...
S-Stay back!
That princess is a bit of a schemer,
but she's smart.
She's far better than the likes of you,
only concerned with self-preservation.
Goodbye, Your Majesty.
Wh-What was that?
There's someone on the ground!
Y-Your Majesty!
Call for help! And fast! Hurry!
Got it!
King Remonas fell to his death.
It was thought that he drunkenly
slipped from the balcony,
but so as not to tarnish his image,
the people were told he suffered
a sudden heart malady.
I can't believe the king is dead.
Right after our award ceremony, no less.
He seemed in good health to me.
If he'd died a day sooner,
we would've had to wait for the medal.
I hate to say it,
but I'm grateful he held out.
But Princess Milena will be crowned soon,
so there's nothing to worry about.
You're engaged?
Yes. Apparently I have a fiancé.
I'm engaged to Third Prince Maiser
Leng Gargan of the Gargan Empire.
The Gargan Empire?
Zirgus once quarreled with the Gargan Empire
for control over the territory of Karan.
Ultimately, Karan went to Zirgus,
but in exchange,
I was secretly promised to Prince Maiser.
So this is a strategic marriage to effectively
force an alliance between the nations.
However, I'm thinking of formally
turning down the engagement.
But then what will happen to Karan?
Karan will remain a vassal
city-state of Zirgus.
Ostensibly, the engagement
and Karan are unrelated.
No official documents were
exchanged regarding the proposal.
I can simply say the situation has changed.
I'd like you to inform Karan's governor
that the engagement is being called off
and obtain his approval.
What is it? Something on your mind?
Yeah. I don't know how
the Gargan Empire will respond.
It's hard to come up with a plan.
Well, this is just speculation,
but it's possible Karan is experiencing
problems other than with the empire.
What do you mean?
The king of their neighboring
suzerain nation died,
but the governor of the vassal city-state
didn't bother to show.
Don't you find that odd?
You're right.
I'd say the princess's silence
on the matter proves it.
Something's afoot in Karan,
and she's hoping you'll look into it.
Maybe even resolve it.
So she's testing us.
Does that displease you?
Not at all.
I get to meet the governor of Karan.
This is a good opportunity.
I also want to keep as much distance
between me and the princess as possible.
Well, just take it as meaning
she has high hopes for you.
Yeah, you're right.
You must think me cold, Sir Kyle.
Huh?
To be so unaffected
in spite of just losing my father.
I don't think that.
Naturally, I am sad.
My father was equally kind to both
of his children, and I loved him.
But I fear my father did not reciprocate.
Princess Milena...
Anyway, Sir Kyle,
would you like to join the royal guard?
I'd like you to serve me
formally as my knight.
I-Is that because you want
to keep an eye on me?
It's because I want you at my side.
Th-There's something I have to do.
But if anything happens to you,
I'll come running.
I'm only joking.
But I'm glad I got to see you flustered.
Take care on your travels.
Huh?
She was messing with me?!
What's that about?
He's always been weird.
Princess Milena.
Oh, Ninos.
Have you wrapped the hero around your finger?
You make me sound so wicked.
I'm sure such tactics may be
necessary down the road.
But regardless, I believe we should
keep Sir Kyle on our side.
I'm opposed to the idea.
We know nothing about him.
Ninos, I hope you'll continue to assist me.
Yes, of course.
From now on, I'll be in control of Zirgus.
I must do my best.
Thanks for waiting.
Hey.
Belated though it may be,
congratulations on your medal.
Thanks. Not many people are
talking about it, though.
I'm sure you'll accomplish
even more before long.
So, where's my sword?
Right here.
The craftsman who repaired it said
it looked as if it had seen years of use.
Maybe I was a little rough with it.
This sword isn't bad,
but do you have anything better?
I'm terribly sorry.
That is the highest quality
blade we offer at our shop.
I see. Then I guess I'll manage
with this for the time being.
Thank you.
I can't promise anything, but we'll try to use
our connections to find you a worthy blade.
I'll try not to get my hopes up.
We're on our way to Karan.
Do you know anything about it?
You're going to Karan?
It is a challenging place.
It's effectively run
by the blacksmith's guild.
Their leader practically owns the city.
How should I put this? They've...
caused quite a few problems.
It's made trade with them difficult.
But now that they're a vassal city-state,
we've had much more interaction.
I see.
Thanks.
I'm sure we'll be back, so see you then.
I look forward to it.
Also, given Karan's long history and culture,
their armaments are highly regarded.
You may be able to find a worthy blade there.
The first thing I usually do
in a new town is look for cute girls,
but maybe I'll switch things up
and look for a sword.
But are you sure you don't mind
me finding a sword elsewhere?
We'll find another way
to make money off of you.
I pray you'll have good luck in Karan.
Thanks.
Karan's a mining town, right?
I hope there are lots of cute girls.
I doubt they'll pay you any mind.
Hey!
That's not true!
Just the other day, I got some attention.
Yeah? In what town?
Next Time
To the Blacksmith's Nation
Next time: "To the Blacksmith's Nation."